(Amy:)Maybe next week we could all get together.
(Raj:)Lucy, you don't have to answer that.
(Raj:)Don't put her on the spot,
she hates that. Am I right?
(Raj:)Tell her how much you hate being
put on the spot. Go ahead, tell her.
(Amy:)He's a little nervous...
...because he doesn't think I understand
the severity of your social anxiety.
(Raj:)You can't talk about social anxiety
to someone who has social anxiety...
(Raj:)...it makes them socially anxious.
(Amy:)Excuse me, but I'm a neurobiologist,
I think I'm more qualified than you...
(Amy:)...to understand what's not working
in your girlfriend's brain.
(Raj:)Don't call her my girlfriend.
(Raj:)We haven't discussed whether
we're girlfriend and boyfriend yet.
(Raj:)Now that it's out there...
(Raj:)...are you my girlfriend? By the way,
if you say no, I'll never be happy again.
(Raj:)Not to put you on the spot.
(Lucy:)I think I have to go to the bathroom.
(Raj:)We might as well go ahead and eat.
She's not coming back any time soon.